whye9.ws 2009-08-15

# Privacy Policy - Acme-People-Search.com

If you choose to register for unlocked search results at our Web Site, we ask for your first name and email address so we can send you a confirmation link to create your free search account.  We use your first name and your email address ONLY to correspond with you regarding your search request.

100% of the data that appears in our search results is obtained from third parties. Therefore we are not responsible for the accuracy or completeness of such data.  Since we have no control over the sources of such data, we do not offer any means for you to opt out of the results displayed on our Web Site.

When you visit our Web Site and perform searches, we may collect non-personal information about you, including but not limited to, your computer's IP address, your browser type, the web site that referred you, and your search criterion. This non-personal information may be shared with third parties.

Although our Web Site may contain links to third parties' web sites, we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such third parties' web sites.  You are encouraged to review the privacy policies of these third parties' web sites independently, before you provide them with any personal information.

When you visit our Web site, third parties such as Google AdSense may send cookies to your Web browser, or use beacons to collect information. According to Google: "A 'cookie' is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. When you visit the web site again, the cookie allows that site to recognize your browser. Cookies may store user preferences and other information. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some website features or services may not function properly without cookies."

We use [third-party advertising companies](https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=94149) to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. All changes will be published on this page, which is located here: <http://acme-people-search.com/privacy.php>. If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us online, or at the mailing address below:

Acme-People-Search.com  
Attn.: Privacy Policy  
5505 Connecticut Ave., NW, #101  
Washington, DC 20015
